Guide to the Records of The Weiss & Klau Co. 1892-1988 (Bulk 1922-1968) MS 687
New-York Historical Society
- Series VII: Scrapbooks, Photographs, and Ephemera, 1896-1966, n.d.
  - Photographs, 1924-1926 (Offsite-box 16)
  - Wooden Printing Block, n.d. (Offsite-box 16)